I'm putting out the bean jam.
Oh, you're doing flowers, too?
I'm also doing flowers.
I'm sorry that so many people came to the event, but please move on to YouTube,
We're going to start streaming on YouTube,
We will be streaming on YouTube.
Please come to YouTube.
I'm going to cut this off now.
Aira 300 flowers 60, it's reality.
It's because we started later.
Thank you. Sixty people who came to me, thank you.
Thank you.
75 people came to me because I quit Aira.
I shifted it around a little bit more.
It's true. The number has increased since Aiara quit.
I really hope everyone will move on.
Nice to meet you.
I'm sorry. I'll be streaming on YouTube.
Bye bye, go to YouTube, see you on YouTube.
Let's start. Okay? It's already started.
Okay.
Okay, bye.
If you haven't seen it, let me see it. Yes. Yes. Five seconds.
Four, three, two, one.
[applause]
Is there anything like this open tonight? Would you like to join us?
I've always wanted to talk to you. After the rain, we're still going to have a chatting party.
Let's go. Talking in the rain. We'll talk about candy flash while dancing in the rain.
[Clap] [Clap
Good evening to all of you who are watching our YouTube Live Ameflash Official Channel. Good evening.
We are Ameflash. Good.
Yes. Moeka was in charge of the title this time. Yes.
Let's see. You must be Pyon-san. Pyon-chan-san.
The behind-the-scenes story that we don't get to hear very often. It was worth listening to. I enjoy this kind of times.
I thought it would be nice if there were other staff members.
I'm always so nervous about keywords that I just blow them out of my head and forget about them.
Oh, that's true. But you know what? There were a lot of people who said the keywords.
There were a lot. Last time, when I mentioned the keyword "Mae Takeuchi," she said she would sing at the special selection.
She said she would sing anything. Did they sing the Amehura song?
Yes. We sing different songs. They are singing different songs.
If you sing American Hula songs. I was thinking, "Did I narrow it down to Amehura songs? I thought.
I was told by the audience that they were all Amehura songs.
I thought they were only singing Amehura songs, but they were singing Yuzu and Ponyo.
Ponyo? Ponyo?
Yuzu sang all the fairy tales.
So I thought, "Oh, that's OK," and changed the songs in the middle.
I changed most of the songs to songs from Ame-hora.
But everyone did it.
Thank you so much.
It would certainly be fun to have another meeting with a different staff.
Sure, sure.
But I heard a rumor on Twitter that Mr. Suzuki's was the best.
Maae Takeuchi said that Suzuki's was really good.
It was good.
Is that because it's a song?
No, I mean, did you really think it through?
But Michino, she was full of you.
To have you do it in front of me.
That's mostly what I did.
Sometimes, if there was a request, I would do that.
That's how it was.
I asked them all.
I asked them what they wanted.
I also used the request method.
I sang almost all the time.
Oh, yeah.
They were so happy to hear me sing in front of them.
He was so cute.
I was so happy.
That's the point, isn't it? What should we do?
We listen to what the fans want. It's a request system.
They say it's better this way.
You want everyone to sing as hard as they can?
They say, "It's full of you.
I thought I could hear your voice coming from next to me,
I was singing hard in one piece.
We were doing it together.
If it had been better, I would have gotten them all excited.
It was good after all.
That's how I felt about the title call, the part where I said I've always wanted to talk to you,
We will choose one person from among those who tweeted their thoughts on Ameshabe.One person will be chosen from those who tweet their impressions of Ameshabe.
Please tweet your thoughts on the show with the hashtag Ameshabe.
Best regards.
Okay, then.
Airakireru?
Yoshikazu Mann, the new Mimura Award for raw barley, raw garbage, raw eggs, red pajamas, blue pajamas, yellow pajamas, brown pajamas, like Ron Rik.
You're chewing on it, aren't you?
The Mimura Award for a new species.
I can't say this.
Thank you very much.
And Mr. Toi. The new song is cool and fun. I'm directing.
And, Kosuke-san,
Lilibet. Thank you for your hard work. I'm glad I went it alone.
It's indescribably addictive, and I'm swamped by the production. I'm swamped.
Thank you very much.
Also, I received a message from Mr. Tororo Hishimo to Ms. Aira of AI.
AI?
Yes, something like AI.
I don't understand it well.
In DM or on the Internet, AI is AIRA in English.
Oh, so you mean AIRA?
There are a lot of "Hello, AIRA," or something like that.
She is beautiful like AI, so I put "AI" and "Aira" together.
Is that what you mean?
No, that's not what I meant.
I have no idea what it means.
You mean AIRA, don't you?
Thank you very much.
Yes, I am.
We also have a message from Mr. Yakei.
Enjoy MAC's new coffee shop series.
What's that?
You're doing that now? Retro coffee shop series.
I don't know.
Where?
It's on MAC.
They're doing it.
What is it? The design.
Yeah, it's kind of retro. Like a coffee shop.
Let's take a look later.
I don't know what to do. What about Spacha?
Thank you very much.
So last weekend we held Lily Swift's 5th cup at Raraport and Yutaka's.
So, how about another cup of coffee to recap Lilybe? This is the corner of "How about another cup of coffee?
I don't remember if we had a title like that, but it was my 5th cup of coffee.
I always spend about 20 minutes in this kind of review talk.
I'm not even halfway through.
So I decided to make it a corner.
I made it a corner.
But if you have a lot of announcements, that's all there is to it.
That's right. I decided to make it a corner.
It seems like we can't have a corner every time.
If we make this a corner, it will give the impression that the corner is good.
It will be energetic. It's important.
Once again, thank you very much to everyone who came to the show.
It's been about a year since I saw Raraport and Yutaka. Have you changed? I guess so.
Last year, I felt like the place was empty. I didn't think there were many people there,
The day before yesterday?
When I saw Raraport and Yutaka this year, there were a lot of people who came to see the show.
Mom said she wanted a lot of people to come, right?
So I was happy to see them.
Because so many people came.
My mom's mom said. She said that your mom was always smiling, and that it was so cute to see her smiling at Mr. Yutaka.
She was happy.
I'm so embarrassed. My mom took a picture in front of Kimura's poster. It's the worst.
When everyone was having fun with Raraport like this.
Did you have a poster like that?
You could see it from us. To the left.
It's really embarrassing.
It's like the mom of love.
There were a lot of people who were interested in the first, second, and third parts of the show and came around to look at them,
I heard later that many people came to get flyers and stuff like that.
I was really happy to hear that.
I heard afterwards that there were many people who came to pick up flyers and other things, which made me very happy. It was the first time for me to go around the perimeter.
I heard that about the same number of people came as Norisagari-san and Skill-chan.
So we were a little short of our goal.
We were almost there.
Our goal is to mobilize 500 people. Within this release.Our goal is to mobilize 500 people. Within this releve.
People who stopped and came and stopped in that first part,
There's a second part. So some of them came back for the second part.
It's amazing to think so.
People who obviously didn't know Amefurashi came to see us during the second part of the show.
They even came to the benefit,
I was happy to think that maybe I had made a big impression on them.
It made me happy. I was really happy.
But I also covered a song by Chutoku Express,
I announced it a little beforehand,
I was really happy that so many people from Yagoshikuruma came to the event.
I was really happy. And they all had T-shirts,
The T-shirts that Kaikun was selling.
I was so happy to see that they were from Yagoso Kuruma,
I recognized you as Mr. Yagokuruma, so I was very happy.
That's it. The people who came to the show also had tickets for the bio-signing.
I'm so happy,
I'm so happy. I'm too happy.
I'm really happy that they come to Amefurashi's live concert even a little,
I understand now.
I'll take the liberty of deciding now.
What is it?
Yagokuruma-san equals Amefura's customers.
That's not good.
That's bad, too.
I've already said that to 500 Lilit customers.
From now on, when you find a person who writes "Yagoshikar" on his/her Twitter prefilter, you can say "Thank you very much for your support,
Thank you for your support.
Not at all.
You might not like me.
But I knew it.
Who are you?
Because the fans of Amefura are also Yagokuruma.
Oh, you know what? Exchange situation.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm not good at it. I'm not good at it.
I can't contribute, so that's that.
We're too positive, though,
Yeah, yeah.
I know, I know, but I look at the Twitter prefiles every time,
I even want to make a lip-sync thank you.
Thank you for your support.
Even if you've never been to one of our shows, come to one of our shows.
I've never been to a show before, so I'll just say, "Who the heck are you?
Well, I'll just say so.
That's how much I'm losing steam.
That's right. That's right.
No, no, no, no. I'd be happy if you said you're fine with that mindset.
I'm saying I'm a Yago car.
Oh, you mean?
I'm so happy.
You're the one who always comes.
Look, look, look.
I got it from a guy named Mr. Shio.
It's a Yago car. He said it's a cute burner and it was great.
Yay!
Thank you very much.
That means..,
Does that mean we can use equals or something?
Is that okay?
Don't get carried away.
No, I don't think so.
But you know, I thought about that when we were in Thailand,
I thought it was just the two of us singing together,
And they had more than twice as many people as Ayala and her group,
And they were all dancing in unison.
I thought it was really amazing.
I was so breathless while singing along.
I was so excited.
I don't know,
I don't know how to say it.
If you ask if we had a lot of relationships with our seniors, we didn't have any.
I have had the opportunity to dance behind Momokura-san as a back-up dancer,
I had a lot of experiences like that,
But I never had a chance to perform with my seniors,
So I was really happy that Jyoshogakkyu-san gave me such an opportunity to perform with him,
From that point on, I couldn't stop respecting him.
I can't stop.
I can't stop respecting them. I really can't stop respecting them.
So I was thinking, "They've been saying that for a long time.So I'm thinking, "They've been saying this for a long time.
I'm thinking.
They are fans, aren't they?
We are so happy to hear that.
There are even people from Car 8 who have become interested in us through TikTok,
I'm so happy.
There are also people who have just met us.
Wow! Good evening.
Good evening. Thank you very much.
I'm so glad you found us and checked us out.
I'm so glad.
Thank you.
I'm so glad. Please check us out again.
But I'd like to cover something again, wouldn't you?
Yes, that's right.
I'm sure the Amefura fans would be happy with a cover.
That's right.
If you ask me, Amefura is the No. 8 car right now.
That's true.
I don't know what to say. I'm sorry.
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know.
I don't know what the angle is,
I don't know what the angle is, but if it reaches the person in question,
I don't know what kind of angle it's coming from, but if it reaches you, you're doing it as car No. 8.
I feel as if I have to touch them.
I feel sorry.
I do it because I like it.
Please don't worry about it.
Please ignore it.
It's like I'm doing it as a fan.
Please just ignore it, really.
So if you're pissed off, just say you're pissed off.
Really, really.
Please don't do it.
I'm not listening to anything.
I'm in the mood that I have to accept it.
I'm sorry.
Please tell me that you didn't want me to do it and that you don't want me to do it.
Tell me I'm not allowed to do this.
But this re-release, the last re-release in Diversity,
We covered E-Girl's song,
Or we covered a song by SMAP,
Or, in the case of Lalaport, we covered NiziU's song,
Or cover ZADZAD with just the dance moves,
It's something only a re-leave can do, isn't it? Cover songs are really important.
Yes, that's right. Everyone is looking forward to it.
Oh, you saw it for the first time yesterday in the comments.
Yay!
I'm so happy.
Where did you do that?
Where did you get it from, Mr. Whitestreet?
Maybe he saw me on TikTok or something.
I'm so happy.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad.
Is it difficult? A little.
It's difficult.
Some of the songs are for men, and we are women,
There are high notes and high notes,
And the dancing is also very high level,
It was hard for the four of us to do it.
But it was fun.
Because it requires a lot of physical strength. What can I say?
Really.
Like a man's physical strength,
You have to have a lot of energy,
It's difficult for us to dance coolly, isn't it?
It's very difficult to dance coolly and intensely, isn't it?
We had to have some "hāmori" (harmony).
You were doing it for sure, right, Mayuka?
It was difficult.
That's right.
With a groove.
In the groove.
Fun.
If that's the case, it's cool.
It's cool if it's all in the groove.
You practiced a lot, right?
Yes, I did.Yes, yes.
I really didn't know. So I listened to it a lot,
I was listening to it all the time together.
I couldn't understand the sound.
Yes.
We practiced a lot, but it was still difficult,
I thought it was amazing.
I really thought it was amazing.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry for covering your song.
Thank you very much.
Also, you know what else?
You performed our new song, "Sound Twister.
Yes, that's right.
Sound Twister.
This is a very interesting song.
It's about fast-talking words.
It's a song that I was doing a portmanteau of.
It was just like that, but it's a quick word.
It's a fast speech.
But I'd like to talk more about this new song in the next section,
It's all about the satsukar, isn't it? I'll tell you more about this new song in the next section.
So I was really nervous that we would be filmed performing the song for the first time.
I really couldn't make any mistakes.
I couldn't make any mistakes.
I didn't want that part to be filmed.
It's true.
I didn't want them to film only the new song.
I was a little nervous about the other ones, too.
Of course.
I get more nervous when I think I'm being filmed.
My face.
But then there was that satsukar, and this time, there is a lot going on at Lalaporte in particular.
I am exposed.
You have the image that there are a lot of photos of you in various places, don't you?
Yes, indeed.
U Turnapar чего.
I've been wondering if there's going to be a continuation of the Tik-Tok, and I know there's been a lot of buzz about it, and yes, I know, and that's why I've been thinking about the videos that you guys have been taking.
I'm sure it's going to continue.
Yes, it's true.
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much for all the TikToks and pictures and stuff.
I hope this momentum will help spread the word about Rain Flash.
I'd like to do a quick word challenge or something.
But you know... last year, Ira's miraculous photo as Dr. Rapport got a lot of attention.
So I said let's do it again this year... and we did it again this year... but with yuzu...
Well, to tell you the truth, Ai Ra's buzz this time was amazing! I saw Ai Ra's Miracle Photos on Twitter.
I saw that Aira was tweeting a lot of miraculous pictures, and she tweeted a lot of miraculous pictures this time too.
I tried again, just like last year... yes, I did get a lot of likes, but not as many as I expected.
I'm so cute! Didn't you say I'm cute? What's that?
I couldn't find it. It's cute.
But the one she's giving you has more likes, but isn't the previous 139 pretty great?
I'm so glad I checked, because I'm going to have to try it.
I thought it was really, really cute.
I showed him the water, and he didn't even look at my likes, he just looked up "candy lattes.
I thought this one was really cute, so I saved it. Isn't it really cute?
It's a nice picture. Yes, I thought it was really cute.
Thank you very much.
When I took the picture, there were a few more.
Wow, I'm so happy.
That's great.
But it's kind of nice. You got it, didn't you?
It's so cute.
Thank you very much.
It's super cute.
This one of Yuzu is one of my favorite pictures of this release.
Thank you.
It's so cute.
Do you want to have some kind of photo award after the release?
I want to do it.
I'd love to.
But all the photos are so good that I'm not sure if I want to include them all.
There are so many good photos.
Everyone's photos are getting better and better,
They were good in the past, but they are still getting better and better,
I can't choose just one, they are all so good.
There are so many good photos.
I think Yuushatarou is good.
Really?
Yes, it is.
Just now, Mr. Hashimoto was taking a ride to Tokyo and other places.Just now, I heard that Tokyo and Mr. Hashimoto are going to take a flight car.
Wow, that's nice.
It's fine.
Please give us a ride.
That's right. For the breaststroke, we need a car.
I've padded it out to 400 people or something.
Oh, that's terrible.
I said less than 400 people.
I see.
That's fine.
Weakness is a matter of taste.
It was fun, wasn't it?
It was fun.
Morimitsu's photos were good, too, that's for sure.
It was really cute.
It was like a movie.
Morimitsu-san was really in the groove.
It was really interesting.
The movie was really interesting.
It's of Mr. Malaysia.
Yuzu was filming Morimitsu the whole time.
It was too funny.
It was fun.
So you did it, right?
Now, please give me more.
But we'll talk about the new songs later.
If there's one thing I regret..,
If there is one thing I regret, I would be happy if you would like to like our picture in Angels.
Yuzu and Yuzuhana also did something together, aiming for a miracle.
We were convinced that the two of us doing Janga Janga together was going to be an absolute buzzkill.
This was the only way.
Yes, let's do it.
Let's do it.
I want to see it. I want to see it. Let's do it.
By the way. You think so now because you didn't see that scene.
It was super slippery.
You know, it was the first time I saw Yuzu and Hana slip so much.
Because I was holding the camera, it was a scene.
Everyone around us is my family.
I got into a lot of accidents.
I mean, really, there are people who slip a little more and still get a little excited, one or two people, but there were none of them.
But there were none of them.
It was a scene.
Let's do Yuzuka, and then Ayanan or Rika.
What?
No, no, no.
We'll do it first.
It's not fair. You're slipping for sure.
What's that?
It's not fair.
Let's go for now. Please take a miraculous picture.
Janga janga janga janga janga janga janga janga janga janga janga janga.
Thank you very much.
Oh no, I don't want to do it.
You're so cute.
Take out the eyes.
I don't want to do it.
Senpai.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Take a miracle shot.
It doesn't have to be a janga-janga.
I'll go out alone oonse
Um, U.tai lisatz or something.
Do it already.
U.tai lisatz.
I can't see.
I can't see you.
You're just sleeping.
I'm just sleeping.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Janga-janga-janga-janga.
Let's go back to the front one more time.
Okay, everyone.
Take a miracle picture.
Here we go.
Janga-janga-janga-janga.
No.
No.I can't.
I'll never make it.
I can't do it.
I don't know...
We're trying so hard.
We're doing it!
This is going viral.
I really don't like it.
They were practicing.
I mean, they practiced it so hard, they even slipped.
We can afford it.
This is just practice.
These four are too scary.
This is practice.
I don't have any practice.
Let's each do it twice.
If we do it twice, we'll do it the first time.
I'll do the second one first.
Where?
In.
Janger...
Why did you try to do it twice?
I'm sorry.
I don't want to do this anymore.
Because you're going to take this?
You knew it would slip.
Why did you decide to try twice?
It's so long.
It really surprised me.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
What are we going to do when people see this for the first time?
They're so boring.
I'm going to turn down the heat on Monday after the weekend.
Oh, my God.
It's okay. It's okay.
I got you.
This is the kind of fun release we're looking for, isn't it?
Where was the next one?
Next time.
The next one is on Thursday, May 4th.
It's called Girls Dawn in Fukuoka.
I'll be performing separately.
It'll be a kind of a release as well.
It's called Fukuoka Pocket.
It's at Fukuoka Pocket.
It's not only for Amura, but also for other people.
It's going to be treated as a release.
And the next day, Friday, May 5th.
Tower Records Shibuya B1
CUT UP Studio in Tower Records Shibuya B1.
I always say CUT!
CUT UP Studio
There will be two sessions, one at 5pm and the other at 8pm.
Please come and play if you like!
Thank you very much!
Golden Week 4 and 5
So you're coming back to Tokyo after your trip to Fukuoka?
That's right.
It's fine if one of us is closer to home.
We'd be happy if you could come to either one if you'd like to do a satellite tour with us.
If you came to Toyosu, we'd love to see you there.
I'll be waiting for you.
I'd love to meet you by DM or something.
I don't know when.
I don't know what time I'll be there.
I've been getting a lot of comments.
So please spread the word.
Please spread the word!
Thank you!
Shibuya
I don't know...
Fukuoka...
Fukuoka is at 12:00 and 16:00, right?
But on the 5th, at Tower Records in Shibuya...
5pm and 8pm.
This is the reason why
Even if you want to stay overnight...Even if you decide to stay the night.
I came back in the morning and said I can come back to Tower Records again.
From Fukuoka.
I see.
I want to relax in Fukuoka and stay overnight.
So if you can't go the next day...
You can go home.
I see.
It's 5:00 p.m.
You can go.
That's for sure.
That's very kind of you.
We'll be there.
If we eat all kinds of food in Fukuoka...
I'm going to be hungry.
It's just in time.
I don't think he's thinking about that.
That's the thing.
That's why.
I'm in grad school now.
That's why
I'm going to be late.
But there's a lot going on.
I have a lot of things
I'd like to announce...
I'd like to announce all of them, but here's the information about the re-releases.
Yay!
I've been waiting for it.
As I said, I'll be in Fukuoka on May 4th.
May 4th in Fukuoka
May 5th at Tower Records Shibuya
but
May 6 is also the open recording of Amefura Night.
I'll pre-order the CD, so...
Can I see you before the show?
Oh, sure.
In front.
Show them one by one.
Shift them one by one.
Ending roll
Ending roll.
How many are these?
Entry/exit
I don't know.
Yes, I know.
I know what "in-body separation" is.
That's enough.
I'm not following you.
I know what "in-body separation" is.
Definitely not.
I know what this is.
I know what "in-body rendezvous" is.
I know the story.
Are you sure? You're not following me? There.
No, I know what it is.
You don't have to dig.
I just wanted you to know that I know.
You can do it when we're done.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It doesn't matter now.
I'm getting carried away.
You're out of control.
Do your thing.
You're in over your head.
I'm in. I'm in.
Good, good, good, good, good.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I'll do it myself.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Sorry for the wait, ladies and gentlemen.
I'm sorry.
This way.
I'll be at the Amefradite on May 6th.
We'll be selling pre-orders, so it'll be like using a Delibear.
And the same for the May 7th Cup 1 Applegate.
We'll be using Delibear.
We'll be selling CDs.
So, why don't we have a stamp rally, and everyone can eat?Why can we eat the stamp rally?
Yes, you can!
We hope you will come.
Please come.
After that, on May 14, there will be a releve at a certain place in Saitama at 12:00pm and 3:00pm.
Oh! Saitama!
Saitama?
I wonder where it is.
Do you mean a gutsy release?
Yes, I think so. We are going to do only gutsy re-live here,
When we do it in Saitama, we have only one thing in mind.
That's right.
What? Where?
Isn't it Seibuen?
Seibuen? Seibuen?
Seibuen is also nice.
Or maybe Casualty Park.
Kasukabe?
I've never been there.
This is Shin-chan.
I'm sure there will be somewhere, so I hope you can come.
The next one is Tuesday, May 16th at 7pm at the Cut Up Studio at Power Record Shibuya Beach.
This is the day of the coffee album release.
It will be on the same day.
Oh! I've been waiting for this.
This one starts at night. It's a weekday so I hope you can come since it's after work.
After that, the next two days in a row, we will launch at 7:00 p.m. at the cut-up studio at Power Recode Shibuya Beach.
Congratulations! So we would like to do it again two days in a row.
I'm so happy!
Two days in a row.
Yay!
This way.
Well, to be honest, it's two days in a row.
If everyone kept looping forever, it would be 7pm the next day.
So long!
Physical strength, physical strength.
I'm sorry, Hana-chan gets in a bad mood if she can't eat her dinner.
While eating.
I might get sleepy.
While sleeping.
I'll want to go to the bathroom.
From behind.
Stop.
I think it will be the next day.
But I think I won't have to go home.
That's true.
Will we save money on transportation?
I don't think so. Everyone's at work.
Go home, everyone.
We're staying.
You're staying?
Don't we have to go home?
Why not just stay the night?
It's a good idea.
It's on sale.
Why not?
We should do an insta-live or something.
I want to do it! Let's do an insta-live! Stay here.
Whose place?
Whose place are you going to?
Let's decide later.
It's going to be so much trouble.
I don't like it when you look like you want to stay at my place.
I want to go to Yuzu's house!
I want to go to Yuzu's house.
It's okay if you say it's okay too, Mom. I'm fine.
We don't have that kind of fun.
Yes!
Sounds fun!
Let's listen to coffee and drink it.
Let's all talk about it.
I can tell you.
By the way, it's okay. Because it's the release date.
I want to be in good condition, but I have time.
It's good to go on a diet together.
Dinner is a system.
It's impossible. Yuzu's place serves a lot of food, right?
That's right, you don't have to eat.
Then why don't you go to Momoikan's?
You don't say that!
It's okay if you don't eat. Even if it comes out.You don't have to eat it. Even if it comes out.
I can't. I can't do the skin.
It's a special course in the morning.
Full course?
Yes, it's the Yuzunchi Special Course.
Oh, no.
Can I come too?
Do you want to come over for dinner?
I'll be in trouble if I don't. I really have to go.
A lot of it.
I think I'll go to my place then.
I don't want to miss dinner.
I'll have to tell them.
I'll go if I can.
You're not coming.
I'll go if I can. Don't come.
I hope everyone is looking forward to seeing what will happen.
We have a date set for June.
I don't know why.
We are still working on Sunday, June 4, but I think there will be a release.
We are still making arrangements in the Kanto area, but we are not sure what will happen since we are still working on it,
At this stage, I think it will be in the Kanto area.
Kanto. That's a pretty big area.
I'm sorry if it turns out to be in Hokkaido or somewhere else.
I'm sorry if we end up in Hokkaido or somewhere like that.
I don't know. But I'm wondering if it will be somewhere in Kanto. I'm not sure,
On Sunday, June 11, from 12:00 pm, Aichi Boys!
I wonder where it is?
Sorry for the wait.
Finally, I can go.
Aichi Prefecture?
I've been asked to come to Nagoya and Aichi, but this time..,
Ghibli Park?
Not Nagoya.
I was hoping to do it in the open air, somewhere with a nice view.
Isn't that right?
The place where Aiura got stabbed by a bowl?
Ghibli Park?
Don't just smell it on me.
It's one step forward. Just don't make it about Ai Ra.
I thought the bowl was okay since you said it was outdoors.
You're lying.
I know people who know people who know people who know people.
We've finished the first corner, right? Aira's corner with the smell.
It's over.
I'm sorry!
It was a little different from usual.
I hope we can make it in the right place.
I hope everyone is looking forward to it.
Please do.
Please take the last one with you when you take pictures of the major surfaces.
I will do so. Please come and visit us.
Please do.
Then, let's do this one too, shall we?
Yes, I will.
I'll go first.
Tomorrow, I'm going to talk to Tokin Abert.
Is that how it's going to be?
I think it would be a little different if it was scripted.
I just asked next to him and he said it's fine.
I'll see you later.
Then we'll do it that way.
I'm totally fine with the MC.
Go ahead.
I'll do it.
It's become a tradition.
We'll have a secret password for the next meeting.
That's great. I was going to do away with the secret password.
When all the announcements are done, I'm going to bang.
It's this secret word,
If you say it in the next music video, we'll do something.
So, this time.
You are scoring now, right?
That's right.
What did you do?
What was it last time?
Last time I said it was Mai Takeuchi,
What's your name, Dodo?
That's right.That's right.
If they say it, we'll sing whatever song we want.
Score.
And before that?
Before that,
Everyone was different.
If they declared their love for us, we would tell them we loved them,
That kind of thing.
Yes.
It was only for people who had seen the candy chat.
I was afraid that not many people would come, but surprisingly, many did.
There were quite a few.
Maybe it was because of the previous event.
I guess it was good last time.
The singing was good.
The singing was really good.
I'm glad.
Yeah, I'm glad.
So what do you say?
What's the word?
What's the password?
Amerate, Amerate, Amerate.
Oh!
What about you, Meguchi?
It's amerateraterate amerate.
I thought I'd let you guys decide on the benefits.
Can I chew this?
No, you can't bite it.
Is it invalid?
Null and void?
If I get in line one more time, do I have a chance?
Yes, you have a chance.
Oh, I see.
You have to go through the line again.
But only once if you succeed.
This is the only one time you can use it,
If you bite it, they can re-line it one more time.
So I can do it many times?
Then you can do it as many times as you want.
But once you do it once, you're done.
Why did you bother to write that on the cup?
What? Writing?
I said, "Let's write it like that.
Amelate, amelate, amelate.
Yes, I'm sorry.
The bottom is poku.
Poku below.
Thank you for waiting.
I am ameratete ameratete.
I won't say it. They never say it down to the bottom.
I slipped. If you don't get it going, it looks like I slipped.
I'm going to throw in a little bit of a scrub.
Yes, I'll do that.
Thank you for your hard work.
You know, I'm getting used to writing on this cup, aren't I?
Yes, I guess so.
You never get used to it.
Really?
You get used to it, you don't get used to it.
Isn't it hard?
I couldn't write at all at first.
It's all kind of squishy.
Yes, it's squishy.
Squishy.
That's for sure.
Please practice a lot before you come.
Because your intuition will become the other side.
Yes.
What will you do then? What about scoring?
What do we do?
What will we do for you if you tell us this?
What do you want?
You sang it, didn't you? I don't know. I wonder what would make you happy. Do you want to dance? Dance? Dance because I sang?
What? What? What do you want? Do you want to dance? Or...
Or you can say, "I hate you, please. Oh, it's coming janga-janga-janga-janga.
I'll never choose. I'll never choose. I'll never choose it.
It's not good. JUNGA JUNGA JUNGA JUNGA.
From our point of view, it's totally fine.
JUNGA JUNGA JUNGA JUNGA.
JUNGA JUNGA JUNGA?
Eh? I don't like that. Maybe a fast word?What? That's a little disgusting. Maybe a few words?
But, well, well, well... dancing or janga-janga-janga-janga... or fast speech, custom downstairs...
Recommendations? Teach? Something I've never said before?
Yes? Special customization. A funny face. A funny face.
I don't know.
I don't know. Ilan will decide. I'll make him dance.
I can't decide at all, so I'll make him dance.
I'll have everyone tell me with their requests and so on,
I'll ask them to decide, too, and please use songs we can dance to or songs we've danced to before.
Please do that.
So, please say amelatete amelatete.
I'll be waiting.
I would like to make a new announcement that there will be many more events during the Golden Week holidays and so on,
I would like to make this announcement.
First of all, I will be appearing at Token About tomorrow.
This will be my third time.
We will do our best to make the event more exciting with a lot of performers.
After the YouTube broadcast, there will be a talk port as well,
I heard that you can still make reservations, so please come and join us,
We will have a special event with them like a TV tour, so please make reservations,
Please make reservations for the talk port as well.
Please do so.
And May 4, right?
We will be performing at a festival called Girls Zone.
You know, the one I mentioned earlier.
I'm going to be in Fukuoka, and I'm going to appear as a guest,
Tickets are still available, so please come and enjoy Fukuoka with us.
Please come and enjoy Fukuoka with us.
And on May 6, there will be an open recording of Amehura Night at Amehura City.
Tickets are already sold out,
Thank you very much.
If you can come, let's have fun together.
If you can't make it, please look forward to the broadcast.
Thank you very much.
On May 7, Amehura City will be performing at Kabukicho Applegate.
It is also a festival and will be held at ZEPP Shinjuku.
Our live performance will be from 16:00 to 16:25.
The benefit will start at 5:35pm.
Please come to Kabukicho with us, everyone.
Shinjuku.
Please come.
I guess that's it for Molden Week.
That's right.
Seven days.
That's right. Moulden Week is.
May Talking Avert, tomorrow's Talking Avert Day Whirlup is,
Yuzu is not closed for Maulden Week, so please make sure everyone is in the right place.
Yes. Don't go.
Yes.
I said by mistake.
It's possible.
I told him to finish up.
Possible.
Yes, it's possible. And I'm going to perform at the Odaiba Folk Village on May 9.
That's great. Hana-chan.
Hana-chan is all alone in the middle of the big crowd.
I'm in this gap,
I've worked hard on the VTR today, so please take a look.
Please take a look.
And, on May 12, I'll be appearing on Buzz Rhythm.
Oh, yeah.
This is from 25:14 to 26:14,
It says that the air date and time may vary depending on the region,
I would appreciate it if you could follow the details and make sure you don't miss it.
It's been a while since I was on the show, so I was a little nervous.
But I think it turned out great, so please watch it.
Please watch it.
I will also be performing in Masquerade Idol.
It will take place on May 13 at Kanda Square Hall.
The live performance will be from 16:40 to 17:10,
the award meeting is from 5:15pm to 6:15pm,
AmeFlash will be performing amongst the gorgeous idols,
Please come and join us if you can.
Please come and visit us.
And on a personal note,
On Sunday, May 14, at 7:00 p.m,
I will be appearing in an all-star chorus battle on Furi-TV on Sunday, May 14 at 7:00 p.m..
This is a terrestrial program,This is a terrestrial TV program,
It is a program in which teams compete in a chorus,
I am surrounded by a really gorgeous cast of performers,
I am also appearing in this program with Clan Pop's Eve Eve,
I hope you all enjoy the show.
I'll do my best.
Have you finished today?
The recording is over, but the broadcast is on the 14th.
I put it in the time tree as soon as Ira told me.
Really?
I did.
Thank you.
I'm looking forward to it.
Please watch it again.
Yes, I will.
Ayaka Nation 2023 will be held on May 21 at Yokohama Arena,
We will be performing there as well.
I am very happy to be here.
We perform a lot every year, and I'm really looking forward to it.
It's going to be lovely this time, too.
I've received a lot of free videos and stuff.
I'm really excited about what's going to happen,
I hope you will all come and see it,
The AE selection is now open and will be held on April 2.
Oh, it's already over.
It ended yesterday.
It's almost over,
Please look forward to it.
Please do.
I'll do my best.
Jansan.
This is Perfume Probability 100% Happy Amen Cafe, Cookpad Live!
is on May 25th at 7:00 pm.
Yay.
Registration for the show starts tomorrow, May 2, at 4:00 p.m,
The performers this time will be a pair of Yuzu and Moayaka.
I've only done it with Moayaka.
Oh, really?
This will be my second time with Moayaka.
But that was also my second time, and I've only played with Hana.
That's right.
I see. Surprisingly.
So we just need to prepare fire extinguishers and stuff.
Is there going to be a fire?
It's possible.
No, it's not.
Be careful. Don't start a fire.
I'm sorry to call you when you're really busy, so please don't do that.
I'll do my best. I'll do my best.
Don't be a burden to us.
Have fun. It's delicious.
That's right. It's a lot of fun, so I hope you'll come and see it.
Then, jan.
Here's Yuzuki's Hair Fest 2023 at ZEPP Shinjuku on June 3.
E-plus preorder tickets for this one are available until Monday, May 8, and we will be performing in the second part.
I am so glad.
We are looking forward to seeing so many members of the staff, so please come and see us.
Please come and see us.
End?
The end.
We have so many things on the schedule, everyone.
You all forgot to buy something. Which one is it?
I'm sure there's one that everyone forgot to buy.
Please put them all in the time tree and the schedule book right now, and make sure you have bought them.
Please do so.
And as I mentioned in the opening corner, we just unveiled our new song, TURN TWISTER, which is based on the theme of rapid speech.
I hope that Lilybias will be able to bring you more enjoyment of this song in the live performance,
I would like to give an explanation of the song by the members from here on.
I see.
Nice corner.
We haven't had a chance to give a proper explanation of the songs.
That's true. But there are better things written in the script, so why don't you read it?
Then I'll read it to you, Moe.
Moe-kun will read it?
You're good at reading the whole script.
You read the script in its entirety.
Then I will read it.
This corner is about the new song, TURN TWISTER, and the title of the corner is also in the style of a fast-talking word, in reference to the fast-talking words.This is a corner to convey the charm of TURN TWISTER, a new song with a fast-talking word theme, and the corner title is also in the fast-talking word style, after the fast-talking word.
MC Hana Kajimahana. If you can't say the corner title without biting your tongue, this corner will be canceled,
If you can't say the title without biting it, this corner will be canceled and replaced by a new and embarrassing corner, "Nyantoro Push Nyaneko Champion".
I wanted to say something about the cat championship.
I want to give an explanation.
Good luck, Hana.
I want you to do your best for the sake of the cats. We want to do the same.
So, by the way, the title of the corner is Red Ame-hana, Blue Ame-hana, and Kimuakamu.
Why? Why? Why?
I didn't bite.
Why? Why? One more time.
Red candy floss, blue candy floss, yellow candy floss.
There's a reason they bit you.
What is it?
If it was a purple candyfloss, I would've read it.
No, no, no.
Please don't give me an after-the-fact reason.
This section doesn't appeal to me because it doesn't have my color.
Purple is a rumble.
I think you should apologize to Beni for that.
I am sorry.
I know Mr. Takagi.
But it's a little out of the blue,
Do some simple quick words and practice.
You're right, practice is important.
So, first of all,
Yuzu, Hama, and Ira.
You chewed Ira too.
And Ira, three times in a row.
Nama yuzu, nama hana, nama ira, nama yuzu, nama hana, nama hira, nama yuzu, nama yuzu, nama ham, nama ham.
It's not a cured ham.
I don't know.
I don't like it!
It doesn't matter which one it is.
I don't know what a cat championship is.
Yuzu, Yuzu, Hana, Ira, Yuzu, Hana, Hana, Ira, Yuzu, Hana, Hana, well, Hana, ..,
You know that song about the raw ham?
No, no, no, no.
Nama Yuzu, Nama Hana,
Oh, no, this is no good.
It sounds like a raw honeysuckle.
Nama-hana, hana-hana.
Hana-jan-jan.
Yuzu, Yuzu, Hanah, Hanah.
It's no good on the first try.
Let's try something else.
That was difficult.
One more.
I prepared another one.
Choco moka-ka inside a chocolate moka.
I can't put it inside.
I can't get it in the middle.
Choco mokaoka, choco moka inside choco moka.
Choco mo naka choco mo ika.
I would like you to tell me what you are going to say, even if it is slowly.
Yes, I will say it slowly.
Choco mo naka choco no naka choko no naka choko mo ika.
Please say this.
This one looks easy.
Practice.
Choco maka choco no naka choco no choko mokaika.
That's great.
I did it.
Sorry, this isn't the right place.
Keep up the good work, Kojima-san.
Keep up the good work.
Please give me an important corner title.
Red Rain Comes Down
I'm sorry, I misspoke.
You don't have the order. I made a mistake. Can I do it one more time? It's an order, so let me do it instead of handing it or something.
Now, Mr. Kojima of the mc, please give us your important faitre... Red rain down, blue rain down, kiyamari kiyamari red rain flower mahalah chia mela
It's raining blue, it's raining blue, it's raining blue, it's raining blue.
No, it's the cat championship!
Oh no!
What's a cat championship?
The cat championship is just a question of getting in front of the camera and saying "kawaii" to the cat with your eyes cut off 120% at once!
I hate it so much!
I don't have time at home.And I don't have a home time system.
You're right.
You can't say that, can you?
It's raining and we can't do that even though we're idols.
That's true.
So the question is...
We need you to break out the cameras.
That's why Kojima's at the top of the list.
Time is time.
It's a lot of time.
I'll probably only have one person representing me.
Then please do it.
No, I want Yuzu to do it.
It's not that I don't want you to do it, it's just that you made a mistake.
In times like this, I know I can count on you, Yuzu, the mainstay of the rain flurry.
I want you to be the cat with the rain flurry on your back.
I heard from a source...
I heard from a source that you're a fast talker who announces in a vacuum.
You didn't even train to say it.
I practiced.
You're all right.
You're weak at the top if you talk over each other.
I didn't! I didn't!
Kake koke koke koke!
You didn't do it!
Let me make it look like I'm doing it.
I did, but...
You didn't.
You didn't do anything.
I practiced my fast speech.
Hana listened to the soundtrack.
Oh, it'll work.
It's not the best.
I'm scared.
Can you please not make up weird stories?
It's the scariest thing I've ever heard.
I'm trying so hard with my voice to make it sound a little bit wrong.
What's with the flowers?
Oh, I'm sure you can do it.
I didn't.
I didn't even know how to say it in the first place.
I wasn't even holding my breath.
I'm telling you the truth.
You bit it, too.
I'm a tendril.
I didn't bite her.
I loved your hair.
As long as it's pretty.
I'm sorry it's not pretty.
If you're going to bite something...
It's like...
I don't know why it was so good.
On the flower.
Up.
It's the difference in tone of voice.
Please be a cat now.
Is it me?
Yes, ma'am.
Yes?
That's funny.
Get a weight on it.
It's a cat named Munchkin.
Isn't he cute?
Stop it.
You'll make people want to buy it.
Sweet hair, please.
It's not sweet hair. I made a mistake.
Shake it off.
Meow.
Thank you very much.
But I knew this song is not like anything I've ever heard from Amefurashi,
What can I say, it's cool,
Ouch!
What are you doing?
What are you doing?What happened to you out of the blue?
It's getting cute.
I was just explaining the new song.
You just catpunched me.
You just now catpunched me.
That's too scary.
Someone else should do it.
But it's like something you don't see in Ameflasi,
It's like, what's the word?
You!
You're shifting the conversation.
You're shifting the conversation!
I don't care about the cat!
You say more than you mean!
Can I go now?
I can't hold back anymore.
I can't control it.
A new song.
They're over here.
Even the flowers.
I couldn't collect them.
They came this way.
It's a new song.
Hana had the same new song.
I've covered it up.
I've covered it.
I can't stop loving and respecting.
Hana.
I'm in trouble.
The new song is good.
I don't know how to describe it.
It's like they're doing something tacky but doing it in a really cool way.
It's like they're doing something really cool with something that would normally be a bit tacky.
On the contrary, it was like they were dancing along with the spare coffee album.
At first glance, it seems a little off, even though the song itself is a calm song like "Coffee.
But they do it with a relaxed attitude.
It's good.
Smile, grin, grin, grin.
Go home.
I thought he was doing his best.
What is this feeling?
He's trying to change the atmosphere. He's grinning at me, saying he's doing his best.
If that's the case, I want you to come home. Right now.
No one speaks for a long time.
I always thought I should say something.
But this song has a part where everyone can dance together, you know?
You can say it, but you can also imitate the scene where you can say it and dance to it.
There's even some Juliana dancing in it.
And fashionable too.
Maybe some of you have never heard of it.
Want to try it?
The fast-talking part.
Okay, let's start with the last one, "Sumo Sumo Sumo"?
Yeah.
It's not stimulating enough. Let's go!
Dexychu-shu in massachu-shu out of sumomomo-momo.
Red pajamas, blue pajamas, yellow pajamas, and cha-pajamas.
That's the one we did together?
Speed up!
Eggs, raw eggs. Red pajamas, blue pajamas, yellow pajamas, chapajamas.
Rouninnyaan oshinshu sanshinshinjon.
Kaede Peco Peco Peco.
Kikkuri kikkuri mikkuri mikkuri.
Aware of the situation, I will listen to you.
The customer next door listens carefully.
Kara Tokyo Patent.
Kikukurikukuchonbouzu drew a good picture of a monk in the second.
The reason why I put the jidate on this occasion is because I wanted to put the jidate on it.
It looks good. Knock-knock, knock-knock, toshi-shon.
Here it comes!
They all went on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on.
Twist Time All Night All Night
I couldn't say it at all.
It's fun, isn't it?
It seems to change depending on the show. It's pretty good.
That's what I was thinking.
Sorry.Sorry.
This is, you know, we are also
There is a risk that we might say something that is not our part.
Just put it out there. Other people.
Actually, that's the part of the song,
But for the actual performance, other people will do it.
Then, there may be times when other people will say, "Well, go ahead and sing,
If we say it the other way around, we can't say it anymore.
If we can't do this song, we can't do it. If we can't do this song, then we may ask the audience to do it.
If we can't do it, we might have the audience say it,
So, if you want the audience to participate, you definitely have to memorize all the lyrics.
I want you to practice.
Please practice.
Isn't this Takesho 2 the most difficult?
And this Take-sho 2 is the hardest,
This one is the last one, so it's the fastest.
It is the last line.
It's getting faster and faster.
It's really difficult.
When I practiced the second line, I really hated it.
I couldn't say too much.
Yuzu, the other day, I really wondered why I spent so much time on this.
I really wanted to say it, and I was practicing in my room for an hour.
I couldn't say it,
I was like, why did I spend an hour on this when I couldn't say it so well.
I watched anime.
I saw the cartoon.
You should be able to say it.
It's hard. It's all difficult.
But I'm really bad at Takesho.
I used to practice with a metronome or something.
I had to practice a lot with a metronome or something.
I couldn't say it too well.
I was mumbling at home.
I thought I would get sick of it.
This bamboo made it.
He was working on it right before recording.
He's definitely a bad guy.
I'm sure this song will continue to develop.
It's still developing.
It's a developing song.
It's fun to be a part of it.
It's a song that gets better live.
I'm sure everyone is taking videos of it, so please remember it.
Please memorize it.
Also, Ira and Micah are going to play it.
The soundtrack hasn't been released anywhere.
But there is a part of it on TikTok.
The soundtrack was released for the first time on TikTok.
I wrote the chorus.
There is a TikTok where they are doing it.
If you enjoyed it and think you can dance to it, please go to TikTok and dance with me.
I'd be happy if you could dance with me on TikTok.
It's fun, isn't it?
Please dance with us.
That's all for now.
Who's going to say it?
What?
The end of the corner.
Shouldn't the person who couldn't say it say it?
Then let's all say it.
We'll all say it.
Three times?
What's "bang, bang, bang"?
Dong-dong-dong?
Then, let's start with Yuzu and say "bang, bang, bang, bang. If you do it, you can start over forever.
Wow.
So that's it... red rain hula, blue rain hula, yellow rain hula.
Red rain hula, blue rain hula, yellow rain hula.
Yay!
Absolutely no skin, that one.
Number 4, just barely, just barely, just barely.
Something like, ao ao fao fao fao.
I felt like I couldn't even get in just barely.
I can't even say "just barely safe.
I couldn't even close it.
It was just barely not good enough.It was a last-minute failure.
Well then, everyone, meow again. Let's meow one more time.
Let's meow.
Sorry meow.
I don't want to do it. I don't want to do it.
I'm sorry I couldn't say anything.
Oh no. Why do I have so many slips?
I'll shush. That's why I'll shush.
I'm sorry I couldn't say anything.
I won't forgive you!
No!
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye.
What do you mean, "paint the big one"?
It's true.
Now I'd like to go to the last corner.
I guess it's me.
I don't have much time.
Please go.
Don't come out.
Another week, Suiker.
You can say that, can't you?
It's time.
I'm here.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm on a bit of a clock.
I'm sorry you had to come all the way from Dubai.
I came all this way...
I came all this way.
I was just...
I was just asking briefly.
I have to tell you now, right?
I see.
Next is my corner.
Wait and see, Buckarookee Yuztuba.
Why?
Okay, that's it.
It's time for this time.
That's right.
Okay, everyone.
I feel fine.
But, you know, because of this corner...
It's making my family uncomfortable.
I hope you don't mind.
Are you okay?
I'm scared.
Yes, I'm fine.
I might have lied to you today.
What?
Maybe he lied when he said he was going to tell you this today.
It's 9:00 p.m.
You must be feeling a little relieved.
I can't tell you that I haven't had flowers since the 3rd grade. I'm relieved.
I can't say.
I'm not sure if it's a different story, or if the lack of applause is a little awkward, but the member to be made fun of this time is...
Iron Micah!
Yay!
I've been waiting for you!
What?
You two?
Yes, ma'am.
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared.
What? No, you're not!
What?
Not today!
I told you last time.
I told you it was okay to sell to someone else.
I guess you want me to tell you now that they didn't sell.
I still get a lot of information.
So you sold the flowers?
I didn't sell them, I didn't sell them, I didn't sell them.
I didn't sell them. They've all been sold.
I'm scared.
Who's the humanitarian?
Oh, my God, you guys.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
Oh no, what?
Okay, so...Yes, sir.
I heard a rumor...
It's like this.
I'm sure it's you.
He came from Dover and turned around...
Why?
I went this way and took this route.
What?
It's just plain weird!
It happened at Raraport Toyosu.
What?
The day before yesterday.
Not the day before yesterday.
I'm too busy to do anything that could cause an incident like that.
What was it about?
A long time ago.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No more... no more... no more...
And flowers.
I've got lots of flowers.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
What?
Yes.
We've been pretty busy.
We had a lot of special events.
Between the first and second parts of a live show, we're always packed.
We have to prepare for the next one.
But I'm sure new people will come to the event.
I'd like to have time to change my hair between the first and second parts of the event.
That's the worst.
Eh?
Well...
The two of them were asking us what we should do with our hair.
Yuzu, what do you think? "This half updo or this ponytail?
Mr. Suzuki would also ask us.
And there was Ms. Aya, who kept asking if the ponytail should be a little higher.
I was thinking how she kept asking me if the height was a little higher.
Then I happened to be wearing the same ponytail as everyone else.
Ayala had tied her hair in a ponytail first, and then Mayaka tried different ways of tying it, but in the end she decided she wanted a ponytail.
So she tried to put it in a ponytail too.
Well, you should certainly wear your hair the way you want to, but I'm the kind of person who thinks it's better if idols don't wear their hair the same way.
I'm one of those people who think it's better if idols don't have the same hairstyle.
I understand that it doesn't matter because they are different, but you can't tell from the other side, can you?
To be honest, I think you should change your hairstyle.
But Suki said she wanted a ponytail.
But Suki already decided to wear a ponytail, but Ayala has a brain like that.
She doesn't want to wear it, even if they're close in length.
Then she said she'd change her hair.
Even though you taught her first.
He said, "What should I do?" He said, "What should I do?" But he didn't change it in the end.
I was just saying to Ayara, "What are you going to do, but not changing it?
It's a common idol thing, this kind of haircut incident.
I was thinking that we should do it together, and for Aya, it was a little too much.
I understand that, and I told her that I don't like it when idols wear their hair.
Ayala didn't like it, but she actually wore the same hairstyle at the end of the show.
Aya, who was wearing a ponytail, got a lot of buzz on TikTok.
Suzuki's ponytail didn't get any buzz.
Ayaka didn't like it, but for some reason, Mayaka, who had the same haircut, put it in a ponytail.
Aya didn't like it, but for some reason, Mayaka, who had the same haircut, put it in a ponytail.
I was the one who didn't like it at first, but she ended up doing the same thing.
I didn't say that.
I'm just saying that I ended up with the same haircut and now I'm like that.
But this is different... isn't it?
We went out to dinner afterwards, and we wore our hair in ponytails, cute as can be.
We got a lot of attention.
I thought, "I'm going to stop talking about them from now on, because it'll be awkward.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, you're trying to say it better than you're trying to say it crazy.
What do you mean, what do you mean, what is this BACLOS?
You're talking about a haircut and it's an incident.
So, to make matters worse, you and I were playing ponytail ponytail robbery.
We didn't.
Wait that long.
From Hatake's point of view, it was pretty much a war.
I'm just trying to tell you that the two of you in the middle, you know, you give off an air of, "Oh, you're good on the outside, so here you go.
I'm sure they don't really feel that way in their hearts.
Of course it's true, there are times when I want to do something, but I have no choice but to give it up.
Moe-chan, you thought Moe-ka was going to put her ponytail in front of you, didn't you?
What did you honestly think when I said I'd do it in front?
I'm the type of person who doesn't really care.I'm the type of person who really doesn't care.
That's why you don't think I'm good at this type of thing.
I mean, everyone wants to look their best, don't they?
That makes me feel better, so I think everyone should do the hair they want to do.
I see.
So you're that type of person.
So you were like, "Go ahead.
That's right, that's right.
He told Aiara that she could wear whatever she wanted.
Then what did you think when Moeka wore a ponytail after I told her I wore a ponytail?
I didn't like it.
I thought she'd wear a ponytail.
I also put my hair in a ponytail the night before and took a picture of the amount of bangs.
The next morning, I'd do the same amount.
I wasn't sure if I should change my ponytail, but I didn't have time, and I thought it would be okay if I wore it.
So why did you go out to dinner?
That's weird.
Because I've been trying to crack you open for a while now.
So I cracked him open and we went out for drinks.
That's super creepy.
Mix it up with the ponytail.
That's super shitty!
I can't believe you're saying that.
You're saying that.
You must have made him mad at you before that.
I did get him a little mad.
I'm going to get mad.
Hey.
Thank you, Mr. Suzuki.
Mr. Suzuki's pony made my pony stand out more.
We decided to go a long time ago, didn't we?
Lollapalooza.
I'll take the most expensive one here, please.
What are you talking about when you're not here?
We're the same.
Jinga-jangle, jinga-jangle, jinga-jangle.
I'm glad you heard me.
I heard it... the ponies.
I was sitting next to him, eating my dinner, and I was watching him, and he was like, "Oh, my God, this guy...
It wasn't there.
It's really funny, isn't it?
But you guys were trying so hard to change one part of your hair and the other part of your hair that you didn't even have time to eat.
I had these two guys with me, so we had dinner.
I have no way to change it.
I'm sorry.
I'll put it on even if the fake Mr. Holanchucki doesn't answer.
I'm sorry, Mr. Holanchucki.
I'm sorry I'm such a jerk.
I'm sorry for being like this.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Of course there's a reason.
Behind the two ebates.
It's a common idol thing, isn't it?
I'm just trying to be pretty for everyone's sake, but...
Really.
But I wish they would ask me twice a day about my hair style.
How many times have you been asked that?
But wasn't it unusual for you to ask about idols?
No, no, what are you talking about?
They really do ask.
It's amazing.
It's like...
It's really terrible!
Moe face and idols...
Why so much?
I know.
I know... for example... we...
For example, you say, "This one's better.
I don't care anymore.
Say, "This one's better.
Why don't you just say, "Okay, thanks," and be done with it?
We'll ask everyone.
I don't know if that was necessary.
I was asked by Moe-face if I wanted to wear a ponytail.
I said I wanted to wear a ponytail, but I also wanted to wear a half-tail.
But my idol wears a ponytail.
I told him that a different hairstyle would be better.
You put it in a ponytail.
I didn't take it in at all.
No, no, no, no.No, no, no, no, no.
I asked her which one was prettier.
I said the ponytail was prettier, so that's what I did.
I asked my mom what I should do.
I asked her.
My mom loves ponytails.
She loves ponies.
I asked my mom if she thought I should wear a ponytail.
She said I should get a ponytail.
But we, Kanokinko and I, why do we ask so many people?
We asked a lot of people and we want to go with the most popular.
That's right.
Ponytails... are the most common, one at a time, down to the last person.
That's the most.
Half of the time, just one.
Uh-huh.
One.
So you can only ask people twice a day.
I understand.
Yes, sir.
Anyway, it's not even a ponytail.
You should do it.
But I just went long recently.
That's true.
It's growing long all of a sudden.
Suddenly it's growing long.
Stress has made it grow longer.
It's grown a lot.
The stress of being pulled
Stress pulled
Much stress
Stress.
You've got it backwards.
It's a normal stretch.
Yes, sir.
See if you can get a haircut.
I'll try my best.
Yes, so someday we'll all have the same haircut or something.
That would be interesting.
On the contrary.
On the other hand, it would be interesting to have it indoors.
It's nice to meet you... or in a place where you can't see many people...
That's for sure.
Twin-tail hair...
You know, twin tails.
Twintails.
You can do it!
I'm not saying you can do it.
Decide if it's cute or not.
Let's start with Amicon.
So these are twintails.
But if you wear a katsu...
Don't say "katsu"!
Wink wink wink wink.
It's a cute twintail.
That's right.
It's good, right?
I like it.
Ponytail.
But it's been a while.
I've seen ponytails with flowers.
I used to.
It was like this.
Have you ever seen a flower ponytail?
It's that thick.
The amount of hair on the end.
Like a thick roll.
Thick ponytail.
Like a brush.
I thought it would be hard for the makeup artist.
Wait a minute.
Like this.
Like a brush.
Big roll.
But it's pulled so hard by the flower blossoms.
Like this...
That's pretty good
Even if you've only seen it a few times
Even if you've only seen it a few times.
It's a bit of a shock.That was a bit of a shock.
That's why.
I don't do long hair anymore.
I went to Mine the other day.
And she said I had a lot of sticks.
That's right.
I don't usually say things like this.
But everyone misunderstands me.
Some people misunderstand that I have a lot of sticks.
I don't usually say things like this, but...
This is terrible.
The amount of sticks is too much!
I've been told that.
It's really amazing.
Yes, it is.
I'm trying to hold it back.
I'm doing my best.
The flowers are doing their best, too.
Your hair.
You always look the same.
Hana gets the best haircut.
It's the first of the month, and it's empty every time.
Hana changes her hair the most.
She's getting the purest hair.
She's always getting purer.
There were times when I went shorter than once a month.
It's true.
Yes, it's true.
This is how we release them.
Oh my God, Bakuro.
Cute.
No, no, no, no.
I'm always trying to make it better.
That's totally fine.
Just don't get really depressed when you get a bakuro.
It's amazing every time.
I don't know if it's related to that, but...
Yuzu's Instagram is getting smaller and smaller.
It doesn't matter.
I'm not depressed.
I'm just wondering how I'm going to react.
You should make it sound like I enjoy being teased.
It's so delicious.
Thank you so much.
Thank you, Yuzu.
We're losing Yuzu-san.
Yuzu kouhou
We shed cheap tears when we were bakuro.
That's why you make it seem like it's Yuzu's fault.
Let's change that.
It's you.
You.
Let's make it better!
I'm sorry I cried like it was Yuzu's fault again today.
I take a picture of you and Yuzu every time we're done talking.
For the story.
There you go again.
I love Yuzu.
I'm afraid you'll do something to me.
I'm scared.
I'm sure Yuzu is doing something behind the scenes.
He's thinking about it.
That's why I'm most scared of him.
Why?
Even if Yuzu makes me say it.
You just said it so smoothly.
Yuzu is always supporting us, right?
That's right.
I know, right?
Thank you, Yuzu.
Thank you.
I'm shaking I'm shaking
Thank you Yuzu, always
Thank you.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's not the best idea.
Let's not waste time talking about it.
But you know what's the worst part?
Shin-chan is making Yuzu look bad with this script.
It's true.It's true.
I don't mean to make it worse.
I'm not trying to make it worse, but I'm not trying to make it better.
I'm not trying to make it better.
I'm going to step back, but please open the door.
You can go back to Dubai now.
I thought we still have time to talk.
I'm fine.
Let's go to a cafe.
I've got time.
Can I go to the last corner?
Oh, my God, time's up!
Another week, Mr. Stay!
This is how it's going to be.
The gallery is buzzing, isn't it?
If it doesn't rain, they're already anxious about it.
The gallery!
If it doesn't rain... it's late...
Please be ready.
I'm telling you the truth.
This week, Mr. Stay...
When the table flowers were eating...
He asked me to sit on the chair at the table, too.
He's the one who does the hand gesture.
Yes, what's that?
Well then, he's cute!
The flowers only have those strawberry pajamas?
I'm really curious.
There are others.
But it's always strawberries.
Yes, always strawberries in terms of timing.
That's a lie.
It's true.
There is only one.
It's like an aloha-like T-shirt.
That's a lie.
It's true.
That's a lie. I don't care about my pajamas.
I've only seen Hana wearing her strawberry pajamas every time she's with Hana.
Are you really doing it?
Am I wearing those strawberry pajamas?
Every time I get a selfie of myself, I'm wearing strawberry pajamas.
It's either strawberry pajamas or tight-fitting spats.
To the members who send me strawberry pajamas?
We send selfies to each other.
Funny faces?
Is it flowers that they send?
They are indeed strawberry pajamas.
That's a great idea.
When do we start?
Oh, no!
I'm so excited.
I can't get it out!
I'm also taking pictures of all the video calls.
I really can't show it.
Then I'll put out the Yuzu too.
It's fine.
Yuzu is totally fine.
That's not good.
Yuzu is fine, but I don't think it's okay for everyone.
I think it's a bad idea.
I agree.
It's amazing. Yuzu's funny face. Really.
I mean, they're really great together.
They're really great.
Why do they do this so regularly? This.
This is so bad.
It's so slow and slow, it's a little bit dangerous.
It's not good today.
So, that's it for this week, too.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry... I'm sorry... I'm sorry... I'm sorry.
I don't like it.
I really hate it.
If you don't collect the cause of today's most sluggishness only at the end, this sluggishness can only be collected.
It started when you did that twice, didn't it?
Yes. It was because of that.
It's definitely not the same.
We are trying to make sure that it will be finished neatly.
A clean finish? This.
Yes.Yes, I am interested.
Do I have to do two preferential lithos?
No, no. Twice.
I'm scared.
So this time, I'm going to do the "Airamoeka Magic," a spell to make you work harder, is that right?
Yes.
Then, may I ask you to say just this corner at the end?
Yes. I would like to say goodbye to you with the last part, "Airamoeka Magic Corner," a spell to make everyone work hard for a week.
Please do so.
Wouldn't it be better to face sideways?
Please pay great attention from the manager team.
That way, that way, that way.
No, no, no, let's not do that.
Do it right, do it right.
Together.
Let's do it, let's do it, let's do it.
It's not going to end unless we do it.
Let's go.
Rap grandly.
Let's all do it together for the last time.
Let's go.
Let's do it together.
Ame and lithium are ame frashaberry.
Ameshabe for short.
Bye bye.
Sorry about the first time.
whatever you do.
Don't get worked up.
Bye-bye.